

SANKET REDEKAR

SOFTWARE ENGINEER



+91 8286955395



snktredekar@gmail.com



www.sanketredekar.com

Summary

Software Engineer with 3+ years of experience in ecommerce domain in design, analysis, developement of various portals. Goal is to keep learning new technologies and grow deep in field of javascript and UI/UX

Achievements/Certifications

Ingram Micro Hackathon 3rd Place

2019

Certified Scrum Developer

2018

Ingram Micro Hackathon 1st Place

2017

Tantravihar Winners

2016

Microsoft Technology Associate: Web Development Fundamentals

2015

OYE Ngo

2015

ITSA Creative Head

2015

Experience

2016 - present

O Software Engineer @ Ingram Micro SSC Pvt Limited

- $\boldsymbol{\cdot}$ Managed and designed the reseller portal of the company , later on moved on to the quoting tool developed using CRM
- Worked with Agile Methodology and used Git as well as TFS for Version Control on all projects
- During the course of time have worked on various technologies like HTML5,css,javascript,angular, Reactjs for web portal
- Worked on the analytics part of the ecommerce website using google analytics and google tag manager as tools
- Worked and implemented chatbot on the web portal using botengine as tool
- Helped bridge departmental gaps and acquired new skillsets by collaborating closely with different teams during projects

2014 - 2016

Internship and Final Year Project @ IIT Bombay

- Worked as an Intern at IIT Bombay in 3rd year of engineering for project of Virtual Labs
- Presented the project at the inauguration of Digital India Week in July 2015.
- · Worked on project of HelpMaps from IIT-B in final year of engineering
- Technologies used were HTML,CSS,Javascript,PolymerJS,google maps api,single sign on, PhP,mysql

Projects

- No Life Without Cricket (NLWC) a cricket fantasy and blogging website made using ReactJS, bootstrap, HTML, javascript and PHP. (www.nolifewithoutcricket.com)
- · Managed NLWC social media accounts with 128k followers on instagram
- Angular website CRUD operations : https://angular-crud-c64dc.firebaseapp.com/
- React JS WYSIWYG editor : https://react-editor-d3a4a.firebaseapp.com/
- Whatsapp Chatbot for Fifa World Cup 2018 and IPL 2019

Education

Vidyalankar Institute Of Technology (2012 - 2016)
 Bachelor of engineering in Information Technology - CGPA : 7.75

K.C.College , Mumbai Higher Secondary (H.S.C) - 88%

R.M.Bhatt High School , Mumbai
 Secondary Education (S.S.C) - 93.27%

Skills

HTML5 PHP

Bootstrap NodeJS

JS/Jquery Angular

Google Analytics ReactJS

Firebase Dialogflow

Interests











